pageonce.com 2012-11-03

# Pageonce Money & Bills: Free Personal Finance App for Mobile

**3\. We protect the information we collect.**

We take very seriously the privacy of your personal information. We use firewall barriers, SSL 128-bit encryption techniques, and authentication procedures, among others, to maintain the security of your online session and to protect Pageonce accounts and systems from unauthorized access. We may also place cookies and similar files on your hard drive for purposes such as security, to facilitate site navigation, and to personalize your experience on our Site. Our cookies do not identify you by name as an individual or by account number except as described in this Privacy Policy. See the "How we use cookies" section below for more information. 

**4\. How we use the information we collect:**

We may use the information you provide about yourself and about your Third Party Sites to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and Services, to respond to your inquiries about our Services, and to offer you other products, programs, or services that we believe may be of interest to you. 

In order to allow you to use certain Services, we may be required to verify your identity. To do so, we may, directly or through third parties, use information you provide to order a credit report or to verify information you provide against third party databases or through other sources. We may also use your information to verify your identity in the event you contact us for assistance with the Sites or Services. 

In connection with the Bill Payment Service, we may use information you provide on your funding accounts to complete transactions you request via the Bill Payment Service, to verify the existence and condition of your funding accounts, or to assist with the posting of a payment with a payee. We may use information you provide regarding a payee if you ask us to assist with posting of a payment at such payee. 

We may use your information to pre-fill form fields on the Sites for your convenience. 

We may use the checking account and credit card information you provide to confirm your accounts are valid and to access funds from your accounts pursuant to your instructions in connection with our Bill Payment Service or in connection with payment for Services that you subscribe to. 

We may use the information you provide to make bill payments on your behalf if you participate in our Bill Payment Service. For example, if you use our Bill Payment Service, we will use the information you provide us regarding a third party that you receive bills from to verify the validity of your account with that biller and to route payments to that biller pursuant to your instructions, and we will use your payment account details to access the funds in your specified payment account in order to pay the bills that you request be paid to such biller. 

We may use your payment account information to recommend the best payment source. For example, we may recommend that you use a specific credit card to pay a given bill because that card has the lowest APR. 

We may use information you provide about Third Party Sites to provide the Services, which may include accessing the Third Party Sites you select on your behalf, so that we can present the requested information to you. 

In certain situations, we may use or share your personal information:

We may outsource some tasks to affiliated companies or third parties and may share your information with those companies or third parties if reasonably necessary to enable them to assist in fulfilling the requests you make or the transactions you conduct via the Sites, including the operation of certain Site functions and Services that require access to information you supply online. In such cases, if such affiliated companies or third parties acting on our behalf are given access to the information you have supplied to us, we require that the companies abide by our privacy policy and institute safeguards to protect the confidentiality of your information. 

We may use your information for internal analysis such as analyzing user behavior in aggregate for research and marketing purposes. Pageonce may also aggregate transaction data and disclose such data only in aggregate and in a non-personally identifiable manner to third parties for marketing and promotional purposes (e.g., how many users responded to a particular offer). Aggregated information does not identify you individually. 

When you visit our Sites, we may collect technical and navigational information, such as computer browser type, Internet protocol address, pages visited, and average time spent on our Site. This information may be used, for example, to alert you to software compatibility issues, or it may be analyzed to improve our web design and functionality. 

When you use the mobile versions of our Sites, we may collect the unique device identifier assigned to that device by phone makers, carriers, or makers of the operating system (the "Device ID"). Device IDs allow app developers, advertisers, and others to uniquely identify your device for purposes of storing application preferences and other data. We may use your Device ID for security purposes. For example, if you have activated a feature that limits access to a Service from a specific device, our systems will access the Device ID from each device you attempt to access the Service with to determine if the device is the specific authorized device. Additionally, we may use Device IDs to monitor suspicious activity. For example, if we detect that a single account on a Site is being accessed from multiple devices, as determined by tracking the Device IDs that access an account, we may contact the user to ensure that such access has been authorized by the user. Advertisements that appear to you via a Site may be delivered by third party advertisers who may access your Device ID, but we do not provide these advertisers any of your personal information. These advertisers may use the Device ID for purposes of determining appropriate advertisements to display to you on a Site. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of Device IDs by any advertisers. 

Any feedback, questions, comments, suggestions, ideas, or the like that you send to Pageonce will be treated as being non- confidential and nonproprietary, and Pageonce will be free to use such information for any purpose whatsoever including, but not limited to, developing, manufacturing, and marketing products and services incorporating the information. 

If our company or our assets are acquired by another company, or in the event of a merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization, or liquidation, we may transfer, sell, or assign to third parties information concerning your relationship with us, including, without limitation, personally identifiable information that you provide and other information concerning your relationship with us. Such third parties will assume responsibility for the personal information collected by us in connection with our business operations or through our Sites and such third parties will assume the rights and obligations regarding such information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

**5\. Emails from which you may "Opt-Out":**

Pageonce complies with the Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act of 2003. Pageonce provides users periodic Site-related notifications, newsletters, or other information via email. Users may elect to stop receiving such messages at their discretion. If you no longer wish to receive periodic email updates from Pageonce, you may update your account preferences on the Site. You may also follow the unsubscribe instructions included in each promotional email. However, please note that certain Services-related email messages that we send users are necessary for the proper functioning and use of the Services, and users who participate in such Services do not have the ability to opt-out of such email messages. 

**6\. Collection of information by third parties and sponsors:**

In certain cases, you may be directed to a third party site to provide information to complete a transaction in connection with one of our Sites (e.g., to purchase a subscription to a Service). In such cases, any information you provide to such third party sites directly to such third party will be subject to the applicable third party's privacy policy and terms of service. For example, for iPhone and iPad users of our Bill Payment Service, subscriptions to the Bill Payment Service are available as an in-app purchase through the Pageonce Money & Bills app, and such purchases are subject to Apple's applicable terms and conditions and privacy policy. For Android users of our Bill Payment Service, subscriptions to the Bill Payment Service are available via Plimus (or its successors or assigns), and such purchases are subject to Plimus's (or its successors' or assigns') applicable terms and conditions and privacy policy. 

Additionally, the Sites may contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. 

The Sites may contain third party advertisements or offers that are complementary to your use of Pageonce that may be custom matched to you based on information you provided to the Site, queries made through the Site or other information. If you choose to use these separate products or services, disclose information to the providers, or grant them permission to collect information about you, then their use of your information is governed by their privacy policies. You should evaluate their practices before deciding to use their services. 

PAGEONCE DOES NOT CONTROL AND IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR WHAT THIRD PARTIES DO IN CONNECTION WITH THEIR WEBSITES, OR HOW THEY HANDLE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION. PLEASE EXERCISE CAUTION AND CONSULT THE PRIVACY POLICIES POSTED ON EACH THIRD PARTY WEBSITE FOR FURTHER INFORMATION. 

We may use third party service providers to help us analyze certain online activities. For example, these service providers may help us measure the performance of our online promotions or determine Site activity. We do not share any personally identifiable information about our users with these third parties, and these third parties do not collect such information on our behalf. 

Additionally we may utilize third party ad serving networks and their associated tracking functionality to deliver more targeted advertising to our users and to optimize customer acquisition efforts. 

**7\. How we use cookies:**

To enhance your experience with our Sites, many of our pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files that are placed on your computer to store your preferences or for other record-keeping purposes. Cookies and other user tracking mechanisms (e.g., local shared objects), by themselves, do not tell us your email address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at our Site. However, once you choose to furnish us with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie or other tracking mechanism. We may use cookies and other user tracking mechanisms, including "persistent cookies", which will remain on your computer even after you close your browser, to understand Site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our Sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our Site (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our Site), and to save your password in password-protected areas. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services. While most browsers are set to accept cookies and other tracking devices by default, you can set yours to refuse tracking devices or to alert you before accepting them. However, by disabling tracking devices, you may not have access to the entire set of features of our Sites. Your browser manufacturer has information on changing the default setting for your specific browser. 

Pageonce may use standard Internet technology, such as web beacons and similar technologies, to track your use of the Site or to track your response to email messages that we send you in connection with the Sites or Services. Web beacons (sometimes called transparent GIFs, clear GIFs, or web bugs) are small strings of code that provide a way for us to deliver a small graphic image (usually invisible) on a web page or in an email. Web beacons can recognize certain types of information on your computer such as cookies, the time and date a page is viewed, and a description of the page where the web beacon is placed. Pageonce may use web beacons to improve your experience on the Site, including to provide you with content customized to your interests and to understand whether users read email messages and click on links contained within those messages so that the Site can deliver relevant content. Our web beacons may collect some contact information (for example, the email address associated with an email message that contains a web beacon). The Sites also may include third-party web beacons so that these third parties may receive auditing, research, and reporting information about advertisements viewed on the Site. 

We use analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our Mobile Applications on your phone. This software may record information such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the application was downloaded from.

**8\. No guarantees:**

While this Privacy Statement expresses Pageonce's standards for protection of personally identifiable information, Pageonce is not in a position to guarantee that the standards will always be met. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in unintentional disclosure of data. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security and are not responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your personally identifiable information. 

In the unfortunate event that your "personally identifiable information" (as the term or similar terms are defined by any applicable law requiring notice upon a security breach) is compromised, we may notify you by email (at our sole and absolute discretion) to the last email address you have provided us in the most expedient time reasonable under the circumstances; provided, however, delays in notification may occur while we take necessary measures to determine the scope of the breach and restore reasonable integrity to the system as well as for the legitimate needs of law enforcement if notification would impede a criminal investigation. 

**9\. Ownership of data and changes to your personal information:**

Your data belongs to you, and you can remove it anytime you want. To cancel your Pageonce account and delete all account information associated with your account, log in to your account at [www.pageonce.com](http://www.pageonce.com/), click "Settings" then click "Delete My Account". If you ask us to delete your account, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to remove your data from our servers. Despite such removal, portions of your data may remain on our production and back-up servers indefinitely. 

If you wish to access personal information that you have submitted to us or to request the correction of any inaccurate information you have submitted to us, you may correct certain information via your user account. Alternatively, you can send an email that includes your contact information to [privacy@pageonce.com](mailto:privacy@pageonce.com) to request any corrections to your personal information. 

**10\. Public forums:**

We may offer chat rooms, blogs, message boards, or similar public forums where you and other users of our Sites can communicate. Any personally identifiable information you submit on a forum, blog, message board, or chat room on a Site can be viewed and used by other users, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. The protections described in this Privacy Policy do not apply when you provide information (including personal information) in connection with your use of these public forums. We may use personally identifiable and non-personal information about you to identify you with a posting in a public forum. Any information you share in a public forum is public information and may be seen or collected by anyone, including third parties that do not adhere to this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for events arising from the distribution of any information you choose to publicly post or share through our Sites. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at privacy@pageonce.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

**11\. Children:**

The features, services, and other aspects of our Sites requiring the submission of personally identifiable information are not intended for anyone under 18 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13 and believe he or she has disclosed personally identifiable information to us please contact us at privacy@paceonce.com. A parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13 may review and request deletion of such child's personally identifiable information as well as prohibit the use thereof. 

**12\. Your California privacy rights:**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the "Shine The Light" law, permits our customers who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to privacy@paceonce.com. In your request, please attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for our response. Please be aware that not all information sharing is covered by the California Privacy Rights requirements and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response. 

**13\. Changes to this Privacy Policy:**

We regularly re-evaluate our privacy and security policies and adapt them as necessary to deal with new challenges. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please review it frequently. You may review updates to our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy at any time via links on [www.pageonce.com](http://www.pageonce.com/). You agree to accept electronic communications and/or postings of revised versions of this Privacy Policy on [www.pageonce.com](http://www.pageonce.com/) and agree that such electronic communications or postings constitute notice to you of the revised version of this Privacy Policy. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here, by email or by posting a notice on our home page.

**Got Questions?**

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, or if you have any questions or suggestions, you should first contact privacy@pageonce.com. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe [here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint&url=www.pageonce.com). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

For more information regarding privacy you can visit the following sites:
